Argh!
(Leonard:)Raj?
(Sheldon:)I'm busy.
(Sheldon:)Doing what?
(Sheldon:)-You've made your point.
-What do you want, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)I looked over the board,
and it turns out you were right.
-You were wrong?
-I didn't say that.
(Raj:)-That's the only logical inference.
-I didn't say it.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I would like you to come back
and work for me.
(Raj:)For you or with you?
(Sheldon:)In this context,
"for me" could mean "with me."
-I have conditions.
-I reject them all.
(Raj:)I'll take the job.
(Raj:)See you Monday.
(Sheldon:)-Wait. You have to drive me home.
-How did you get here?
(Sheldon:)-I walked.
-So walk home.
(Sheldon:)I can't. There's a big dog outside.
(Sheldon:)We can start thinking about methods
of optimizing the detector...
(Sheldon:)-...for 500 GeV particles.
-All right.